<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Focusath</string>
    <string-array name="activities_array">
        <item>Learn a new skill</item>
        <item>Read a book</item>
        <item>Go for a walk</item>
        <item>Exercise at the gym</item>
        <item>Hang out with a friend or group of friends</item>
        <item>Pick up an instrument</item>
        <item>Play a video game</item>
        <item>Listen to an album</item>
        <item>Bake or cook a new recipe</item>
        <item>Watch a movie</item>
        <item>Go for a run</item>
        <item>Clean your room or house</item>
        <item>Meditate</item>
        <item>Try a new food spot</item>
        <item>Try a new hobby</item>
        <item>Learn about something new</item>
        <item>Take a nap</item>
        <item>Go hiking</item>
        <item>Play a sport</item>
        <item>Meet some new people</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="how_does_it_work_text">Within the next few screens, you will be asked to allow for the app to access app usage data, provide a goal, and three activities of your
        choosing. Once this has been set up, in one-week intervals, the app will compare your usage for the current week with last week, and provide appropriate guidance based on
        said usage. Further information can be found within the Quick Start Guide provided.</string>

    <string name="what_is_app_about_text">This app is my primary research instrument core component of my 4th year Honours Project / Dissertation. The idea of the app is to
        integrate concepts derived from Reality Therapy alongside usage tracking technologies to help address smartphone and social media addiction</string>

    <string name="what_happens_after_text">After the evaluation period has ended, you may uninstall the app (note that you are also free to do so and opt out at any time) or you can
        keep the app and continue using it as normal. Two years afterwards, any data relating to the evaluation period will be permanently removed.</string>

    <string name="how_will_data_used_text">As previously mentioned, no personal information will be captured at any point. The app will only store usage data from the current week
        (and past week, whenever applicable). This data will be sent to myself via a pre-composed email for further analysis and is needed to evaluate the viability of the project
        as a whole.</string>

    <string name="good_usage_text">You\'ve seemed to have decreased your app usage over the week, which is a good thing! Hopefully, by keeping your usage down, it\'s put you closer to
        achieving your set goal (or maybe it already has!)</string>

    <string name="before_using_app_text">To use this application, you must provide permission for the application to access app usage data. No personal information will be captured at
        any point, only usage information related to installed apps will be captured. You may opt out of this by uninstalling the app at this stage and letting myself know.</string>

    <string name="email_button_text">Clicking this button below will pre-compose an email with the current usage stats attached to the email. This must be done on a weekly basis
        (if you have notifications enabled, you will receive a notification whenever the time comes).</string>

    <string name="redefine_goal_settings_text">Click this button below to redefine your goal, you can do this as frequently as you want with no penalty.</string>

    <string name="redefine_activity_text">Click this button below to redefine your activities, you can do this as frequently as you want with no penalty.</string>

    <string name="enter_goal_text">First, you will need to enter a goal. It\'s best to enter a goal that you want to achieve that you think is being delayed by excessive app
        / mobile phone usage. Examples include finishing a university assignment, reaching a new personal best at the gym, or finishing a book.</string>

    <string name="enter_activities_text">Next, type in three of your favourite activities. These can be anything from reading, to hiking, or cooking, anything goes. Some activities
        have also been supplied for you as well.</string>

    <string name="activity_suggestion_screen_text">En-route to achieving your goal, it\'s important to substitute the time formerly spent using your phone with other, healthier activities.
        Remember to give these a go when you have the time.</string>
</resources>